Love brought them together. Will fate tear them apart?
Dear John is a drama, romance, war film directed by Lasse Hallström.
While Sergeant John Tyree is home on two weeks leave from Germany, he meets Savannah after he
dives into the ocean to retrieve Savannah's purse that had fallen off a pier.
John eventually falls in love with Savannah, who promises to
write to him until he returns from overseas.
Savannah Lynn Curtis, played by Amanda Seyfried.
John Tyree, played by Channing Tatum.
Mr. Tyree, played by Richard Jenkins.
Tim Wheddon, played by Henry Thomas.
Noodles, played by D.J. Cotrona.
Rooster, played by Cullen Moss.
Dear John is a 2010 American romantic war drama film directed by Lasse
Hallström, based on the 2006 novel by Nicholas Sparks.
It follows the life of a soldier (Channing Tatum) after he falls
in love with a young woman (Amanda Seyfried).
They decide to exchange letters after he is deployed.
Dear John was released in North America on February
5, 2010, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed $115
million against a $25 million budget.
The film explores themes of army, based on novel or
book, romance, love, u.s. soldier.
The tone is emotional.